Fake high price,
big coupon?
I did have a
company ask
about
they have a local
competitor who
will basically
over inflate
their prices and
then give a
really big
coupon
which is a
strategy
They price their
pump outs at like
$1,200
a pump out
which is a lot
but offered like
a limited time
$500 off coupon
so essentially
their pump outs
end up being like
$700 that was
their question if
I don't do what
they're doing is
that going to put
me behind
and so I like
to always think
of things as a
customer and it's
hard when you own
a business
put yourself in
your customer's
shoes
But if I'm the
customer and I'm
looking around at
prices and I'm
like
Oh
like a $500
coupon
that sounds
really good
If I'm the kind
of customer that
doesn't shop
around
I might just go
for that
But if I'm the
kind of customer
that's going to
look at a couple
of different
places and I see
that that's going
to lower my trust
in that company